<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Raisso</title><link>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/</link><description>Recent content on Raisso</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://raisso.github.io/raisso/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About US</title><link>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/about-us/</guid><description/></item><item><title>It Solution</title><link>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/healthcare-staffing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/healthcare-staffing/</guid><description/></item><item><title>It Solution</title><link>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/it-solutions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/it-solutions/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/privacy-policy/</guid><description>This policy notifies the visitor of our information collection and use online and offline. It is applicable to the information collected from you upon interaction with us.This holds if you are a job applicant, employee and other users of our websites &amp;amp; apps.
Categories of Information The following categories of personal information has been collected from consumers
Identifiers - name, phone number, postal address, telephone number, fax number, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport ID, date of birth, employee ID.</description></item><item><title>TERMS OF SERVICE</title><link>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/terms-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raisso.github.io/raisso/terms-service/</guid><description>THE TERMS OF SERVICE MUST BE READ BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE. For you to visit, peruse, or interact with any content published on the website, or the websites as a whole, reading and accepting the Privacy policy and Terms of service are mandatory and these provisions will be considered accepted if you continue to interact with the webpage. Without doing so, you shall not be eligible to browse the website, and/or interact with any banner, ad, or pop-up pertaining to the same.</description></item></channel></rss>